<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abouts on The budBlog</title>
    <link>http://example.org/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Abouts on The budBlog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 19:22:19 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>This Page</title>
      <link>http://example.org/about/this-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 19:22:19 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/about/this-page/</guid>
      <description>No JavaScript or cookies have been used or hurt in the making of this page.
This page was created and designed from scratch by budRich 2019-2020. It is a Static site generated by Hugo. The ASCII-art banners are generated from the pipe: figlet -f 3d.flf &amp;quot;BANNER_TEXT&amp;quot; | lolcat -f | ansi2html. Where 3d.flf is a figlet-font created by xero.
The brick wall background, is an svg file from Hero Patterns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Budrich</title>
      <link>http://example.org/about/budrich/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 19:22:08 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/about/budrich/</guid>
      <description>I am a default Swedish man. I have a background in mechanical engineering (CNC) and rock&amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo;roll lyfestyle. Currently I am mostly doing computer stuff and play Tetris (NES). I also made this, budlabs thing.
I have a playlist on youtube called bra grejjer, mostly music videos I like. It is a good complement to this document when painting a picture of my identity.
whatever™ || budRich February 2020</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Budlabs</title>
      <link>http://example.org/about/budlabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2012 19:21:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/about/budlabs/</guid>
      <description>budlabs is the banner under which I, budRich, publish my various creations. I thought it would be a good idea to have a mock organization that&amp;rsquo;s more reliable and easier to understand then myself. It was a good idea.
I had just read The Idea Factory when i named it, the name is a play on &amp;ldquo;Bell Labs&amp;quot;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>