<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blog on The budBlog</title>
    <link>https://budrich.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blog on The budBlog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 19:21:55 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://budrich.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Slides</title>
      <link>https://budrich.github.io/blog/2003/make-slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 14:34:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://budrich.github.io/blog/2003/make-slides/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In an 
&lt;a href=&#34;../blog/2003/centered-terminal/&#34;&gt;earlier post&lt;/a&gt;
 I demonstrated how to center a block of text in a terminal. Here we continue to build on that script to create a slide deck.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Centered Terminal</title>
      <link>https://budrich.github.io/blog/2003/centered-terminal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 21:26:07 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://budrich.github.io/blog/2003/centered-terminal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The banners on this page is generated from the output from &lt;code&gt;figlet&lt;/code&gt;.
I  found a fun way to create terminal &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;slides&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo; when figuring out how to center the banners.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SimpleSyntax</title>
      <link>https://budrich.github.io/blog/1804/simplesyntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 16:09:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://budrich.github.io/blog/1804/simplesyntax/</guid>
      <description>I created this simple Sublime Text package to get a simple syntax recognition for files where the syntax isn&amp;rsquo;t obvious. By simple i mean only recognize comments. The most common use-case is dotfiles.
I also added symbols/(sections) definitions. So by adding  &amp;gt;&amp;gt; SECTION NAME after a comment declaration you can easily go to different sections in the file.
The package currently contains four syntaxes:
# | ssHash ! | ssExcla // | ssDslash ; | ssSemi Install the package with PackageControl .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ass divided</title>
      <link>https://budrich.github.io/blog/1712/ass-divided/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2017 12:51:15 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://budrich.github.io/blog/1712/ass-divided/</guid>
      <description>I have divided i3ass in two repositories, i3ass and i3add (i3 additions). My thought is that i3ass will be a more serious set of tools. While i3add will be more experimental and can be seen as a showcase of uses for i3ass. I do use all i3add scripts in my personal, daily workflow.
   i3ass function     i3var  Set or get a i3 variable   i3fyra  An advanced simple gridbased tiling layout   i3run  Run, Raise or hide windows   i3list  List attributes of i3wm   i3get  Return information about i3wm   i3flip  Tabswitching done right   i3add function   i3cast  Create and upload screen recordings   i3Kornhe  Resize windows by moving the corners   i3minimize  Minimize active window   i3monocle  Maximize active window   i3zen  Send windows to the zenter   i3term  Launch a command in a new urxvt window   i3wswp  Switch workspace and wallpaper    Installation i3add will have a installation script similar to the old install.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mouseback</title>
      <link>https://budrich.github.io/blog/1709/mouseback/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 17:20:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://budrich.github.io/blog/1709/mouseback/</guid>
      <description>A while ago I got irritated how messy my i3 config file looked, and I researched alternative hotkey managers. I tried sxhkd and it is a fine piece of code. I got a much cleaner setup of the hotkeys and I could do stuff that i wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to do with i3.
But a couple of days ago, i realized that my i3 config could be just as clean as sxhkd by using variables .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>swedish keyboards</title>
      <link>https://budrich.github.io/blog/1709/swedish-keyboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 17:19:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://budrich.github.io/blog/1709/swedish-keyboards/</guid>
      <description>when I was working as a technical support agent I received several calls from angry men who couldn&amp;rsquo;t find the @ symbol on the keyboard. When I explained that they had to hold Alt-Gr and pressing 2 at the same time, they exploded with anger and told me to tell the technicians to make a new keyboard layout! I explained it&amp;rsquo;s an old standard and agreed it was stupid, but that it would probably never change.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>